

ABOUT ME

I am a Long Beach based illustrator who was born and raised in Istanbul, Turkey. Growing up, I had all kinds of pets from ducks to rabbits. This aspect of my childood inspired me to create the art I make today. I moved to Long Beach permanently when I was 17, and I achivied a Bachelors of Fine Arts degree in illustration/ animation. I was employed as a graphic designer at my university for 3 years where I learned how to put together booklets, flyers etc. which pushed me into combining this knowledge with my art, and eventually making my own books from start to finish.

I love ...

TEA/COFFFE
CONCERTS
TRAVELING
BUNNIES
SPARKLY THINGS
BLANKETS
COLORS
THE BEACH
FOOD

Almira Akin

562-380-5027 | almiraakinl@gmail.com

WORK HISTORY

Graphic Designer California State University Long Beach Long Beach, CA 2020-2023

Made custom illustrations for various departments on campus. Developed creative design for print materials, brochures, banners and signs. Created layouts, concepts and designs for different promotional materials. Made unique logos for campus departments.

Front Desk At Intl. Student Services California State University Long Beach Long Beach, CA 2019-2022

Performed data entry. Assisted and mentored other students. Greeted guests at front desk and engaged in pleasant conversations while managing check-in process. Maintained files and records by implementing effective filing systems that boosted efficiency and organization.

MY SKILLS

Adobe Suite
Art composition
Sequential Imagery
Graphic and media design

Visual Development Project management Microsoft Office Print design and illustration

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Fine Arts:

Illustration/Animation SUB PLAN : Pre-Prodcution

California State University Long Beach August 2018 - May 2023

